Charles Lee Remington Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Charles Lee Remington Archives
1935-2007
ENTAR.000001
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
34
The archives of Charles Lee Remington, accumulated over his lifetime, notably including Yale teaching and research materials.
Remington, Charles Lee, 1922-2007
Biographical Sketch
Charles Lee Remington (b. 1922, d. 2007) spent his early years in Illinois, obtained his Ph.D. from Harvard University in 1948, and joined the Yale University faculty immediately thereafter. He was a curator in the Yale Peabody Museum Division of Entomology and served Yale for 44 years as a professor, retiring from the Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology and the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies in 1992.
During his tenure as its first curator, Remington brought the Entomology Division's holdings from modest beginnings into a world-class insect collection. Remington was an active mentor of entomologists and other biologists of all stripes. At Yale he helped oversee the doctoral and masters degree programs, and senior theses, for over 100 students. He was widely known and respected for his oratory skills and lectures, and taught courses in ecology, evolution, genetics, entomology and bioethics. After his retirement he taught courses that focused on population and the environment, endangered species and the biodiversity crisis.
Remington?s research focused broadly on topics in ecology, genetics and evolution, with particular emphasis on hybridization, endemism, population structure, island biology and animal introductions. He worked and published on a wide variety of arthropods and their relatives, with some favorites being Lepidoptera (especially swallowtail and sulphur butterflies), centipedes, cockroaches and cicadas, and authored an important early treatise on animal and plant hybridization.
In 1947, Remington and the late Harry Clench (Carnegie Museum, Pittsburgh) founded The Lepidopterists' Society, the principal international organization dedicated to fostering collaborative research and exchange on butterflies and moths. He also helped found the Connecticut Entomological Society, the Xerces Society and Zero Population Growth.
Description of the Material
The archives of Charles L. Remington notably include correspondence, Yale lecture materials, Biographical materials, Manuscript materials, etc.
Connecticut; Colorado; USA; Postcards; Letters; Class notes; Calendars; Diaries; Labels; Manuscript materials; Memorabilia; Newspaper clippings; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Correspondence, 1936-2007; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  All of his corespondence.
  - Adams, Paul J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 000005
  - Adams, Phillip Anthony. Est. number items = 21., 1957-1969; 000006
  - Ae, Shigeru Albert. Est. number items = 131., 1951-2005; 000007
  - Agenjo, Ramon. Est. number items = 3., 1950-1971; 000008
  - Ahmad, Muzaffer. Est. number items = 3., 1947-1971; 000009
  - Albrecht, Paul. Est. number items = 5., 1949-1957; 000010
  - Albright, C. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1936; 000011
  - Alder, Julius. Est. number items = 2., 1948; 000012
  - Alexander, Charles P. Est. number items = 104., 1943-1980; 000013
  - Allan, J. David. Est. number items = 3., 1974-1975; 000014
  - Allen, Elsa G. Est. number items = 7., 1950-1961; 000015
  - Allen, John A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915-1916; 000016
  - Amadon, Dean. Est. number items = 2., 1956; 000017
  - Ames, Peter L. Est. number items = 1., 1962; 000018
  - Anderson, C. A. Est. number items = 9; + article and picture of Anderson., 1950-1958; 000019
  - Anderson, Dave. Est. number items = 2., 1977-1978; 000020
  - Anderson, Edgar. Est. number items = 3., 1957-1959; 000021
  - Anderson, John F. Est. number items = 7., 1972; 000022
  - Anderson, Wyatt W. Est. number items = 5., 1972-1989; 000023
  - Arakie, David H. Est. number items = 1., 1966; 000024
  - Araujo, R. L. Est. number items = 5., 1954-1955; 000025
  - Arbogast, Richard T. Est. number items = 12; + map of area where specimen were acquired., 1956-1958; 000026
  - Archbold, Richard. Est. number items = 56., 1954-1962; 000027
  - Arduino, Paola. Est. number items = 1., 1988; 000028
  - Arnett, Ross H. Jr. Est. number items = 11., 1962-1982; 000029
  - Arnold, Francis Richard. Est. number items = 17., 1951-1953; 000030
  - Arnold, Paul H. Est. number items = 2., 1954-1986; 000031
  - Arnold, Richard A. Est. number items = 4., 1973-1983; 000032
  - Arnott, William. Est. number items = 1., 1982; 000033
  - Aronheim, Robert E. Est. number items = 2., 1983; 000034
  - Arott, Howard J. Est. number items = 1., 1963; 000035
  - Asahina, Syoziro. Est. number items = 2., 1958; 000036
  - Asplund, Kenneth K. Est. number items = 25., 1958-1970; 000037
  - Aspook, Ulrike. Est. number items = 2., 1983; 000038
  - Aston, M. J. Est. number items = 4., 1949; 000039
  - Atkinson, Thomas H. Est. number items = 1., 1988; 000040
  - Auffenberg, Walter. Est. number items = 2., 1960; 000041
  - Austin, Edward J. Est. number items =9; + folder with letters from wife (E.J. Austin) 1965--1966., 1955-1962; 000042
  - Baber, Donald L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953; 000043
  - Badger, F. Sidney. Est. number items = 14., 1955-1958; 000044
  - Bailey, Earl G. Est. number items = 2., 1953; 000045
  - Bailey, Norman S. Est. number items = 33., 1948-1980; 000046
  - Baird, Donald. Est. number items = 12., 1983-1988; 000047
  - Bakeless, John. Est. number items = 5; + picture of "a paris bookbinders version of Papilio turnos (glaucus)"., 1955-1966; 000048
  - Baker, Bruce. Est. number items = 5., 1961; 000049
  - Baker, Clement W. Est. number items = 2., 1953; 000050
  - Baker, Edward w. Est. number items = 6., 1947-1948; 000051
  - Baker, Fred. Est. number items = 1-10., 1924; 000052
  - Baker, Natalia Sobko. Est. number items = 2., 1992; 000053
  - Baker, Peter E. Est. number items = 2., 1974; 000054
  - Baker, Richard. Est. number items = 1., 1981; 000055
  - Baker, William K. Est. number items = 6., 1957-1959; 000056
  - Balinsky, B. I. Est. number items = 2., 1956; 000057
  - Banks, Nathan. Est. number items = 4., 1943; 000058
  - Baranowski, Richard M. Est. number items = 1., 1988; 000059
  - Barber, Manley D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925-1926; 000060
  - Bardwell, E. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1920-1922; 000061
  - Barghoorn, Elso S. Est. number items = 4., 1952-1953; 000062
  - Barlet, M. J. Est. number items = 6., 1951-1956; 000063
  - Barnett, Herbert C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941; 000064
  - Barnett, Larry D. Est. number items = 2., 1975; 000065
  - Barnhart, Clyde. Est. number items = 6., 1948-1949; 000066
  - Barr, Thomas C. Jr. Est. number items = 6., 1957-1971; 000067
  - Barr, William F. Est. number items = 2., 1981; 000068
  - Barro, Manuel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1928; 000069
  - Bates, Marston. Est. number items = 1., 1946; 000070
  - Batra, Suzanne W. Est. number items = 3., 1961-1993; 000071
  - Bauer, David L. Est. number items = 62., 1949-1962; 000072
  - Bauerfeind, Robert J. Est. number items = 2., 1991; 000073
  - Baxter, Ronald N. Est. number items = 3; + list of species and prices., 1961; 000074
  - Bayer, Lutz. Est. number items = 4., 1961-1968; 000075
  - Beall, Geoffrey. Est. number items = 20., 1951-1953; 000076
  - Beardsley, John W. Est. number items = 3., 1960; 000077
  - Bednarik, Andrew Fredrick. Est. number items = 7., 1984; 000078
  - Beebe, Ralph. Est. number items = 2., 1953; 000079
  - Bell, Ernest L. Est. number items = 4., 1951-1955; 000080
  - Bellinger, Peter F. Est. number items = 63., 1952-1982; 000081
  - Benjamin, Daniel. Est. number items = 3., 1954-1955; 000082
  - Benoit, Richard. Est. number items = 4., 1949; 000083
  - Benson, Woodruff. Est. number items = 3., 1968-1969; 000084
  - Benyamini, Duby. Est. number items = 2., 1977; 000085
  - Bequaert, Joseph C. Est. number items = 54., 1943-1956; 000086
  - Berenbaum, May. Est. number items = 10; + two sets of pictures and drawings of specimen., 1973-1993; 000087
  - Berg, George H. Est. number items = 3., 1960; 000088
  - Bermudez, Pedro J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1928; 000089
  - Bernard, Gary D. Est. number items = 4; + paper with pictures by Bernard from the Journal of Experimental Biology; summary of research and notes., 1974; 000090
  - Berner, Lewis. Est. number items = 3., 1952-1965; 000091
  - Berry, Dean F. Est. number items = 50+., 1937-1946; 000092
  - Beurie, John C. Est. number items = 1., 1980; 000093
  - Biezanko, Engo C. M. Est. number items = 42., 1954-1974; 000094
  - Bigelow, R. S. Est. number items = 2., 1956; 000095
  - Bird, Charles D. Est. number items = 3., 1955-1956; 000096
  - Bird, Henry. Est. number items = 4., 1953-1956; 000097
  - Bitar, Kamar. Est. number items = 1., 1989; 000098
  - Blackwelder, Richard E. Est. number items = 2., 1950-1957; 000099
  - Blair, Frank W. Est. number items = 8., 1951-1968; 000100
  - Blaisdell, H. L. Est. number items = 9., 1950-1951; 000101
  - Blake, Barbara J. H. Est. number items = 73; + letters of recommendation, thesis outline and research., 1962-1993; 000102
  - Blanchard, Andre. Est. number items = 12; + picture of specimen., 1962-1974; 000103
  - Blassingame, Burton. Est. number items = 1., 1965; 000104
  - Blest, A. David. Est. number items = 2., 1961-1963; 000105
  - Blevins, Tom B. Est. number items = 1., 1944; 000106
  - Bloom, Tom. Est. number items = 2., 1987; 000107
  - Bock, Henry. Est. number items = 1., 1966; 000108
  - Bock, Theodore. Est. number items = 1-10., 1952; 000109
  - Bodenstein, Dietrich H. F. A. Est. number items = 2., 1963; 000110
  - Boell, Edgar J. Est. number items = 36., 1956-1962; 000111
  - Boggess, Preston. Est. number items = 11., 1962-1963; 000112
  - Bognar, L. Est. number items = 2., 1957; 000113
  - Bohart, George E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945; 000114
  - Bohnsack, Kurt K. Est. number items = 6., 1953; 002789
  - Bonet, Frederico. Est. number items = 7., 1948-1953; 000115
  - Bornemissza, G. F. Est. number items = 2., 1956; 000116
  - Borowsky, Richard L. Est. number items = 3., 1986; 000117
  - Borror, Donald J. Est. number items = 2., 1943-1944; 000118
  - Boscoe, William. Est. number items = 3., 1945-1960; 000119
  - Boughner, Jackson L. Est. number items = 2., 1963; 000120
  - Bourgogne, Jean. Est. number items = 10., 1949-1961; 000121
  - Bourquin, Fernando. Est. number items = 6., 1950-1960; 000122
  - Bousfield, E. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 000123
  - Bouton, David W. Est. number items = 26; numerous species lists and prices., 1963-1975; 000124
  - Bowden, Sydney R. Est. number items = 57., 1952-1981; 000125
  - Bowe, Martin. Est. number items = 19., 1944-1967; 000126
  - Bower, Fred. Est. number items = 3., 1986; 000127
  - Bower, H. M. Est. number items = 7., 1942-1962; 000128
  - Bowers, Richard. Est. number items = 2., 1973; 000129
  - Boyd, Brian. Est. number items = 2., 1989; 000130
  - Bracher, R. W. Est. number items = 2., 1957; 000131
  - Bradley, J. Chester. Est. number items = 18., 1946-1954; 000132
  - Bradley, John D. Est. number items = 3., 1966; 000133
  - Brambel, Charles E. Est. number items = 3., 1956; 000134
  - Branger, Georges. Est. number items = 1., 1980; 000135
  - Brass, Leonard J. Est. number items = 58., 1954-1958; 000136
  - Brauer, Norman. Est. number items = 1., 1956; 000137
  - Braun, Annette F. Est. number items = 6., 1955-1961; 000138
  - Brewer, George F. Jo. Est. number items = 14., 1953-1977; 000139
  - Brewster, James. Est. number items = 9., 1943-1953; 000140
  - Breyer, Alberto. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1955; 000141
  - Bridwell, L. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000142
  - Brink, Karen. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000143
  - Brivio, Carlo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986; 000144
  - Brobst, Joyce E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974; 000145
  - Brochin, Sarah. Est. number items = 1-10., 000146
  - Bromley, Stanley W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1941-1947; 000147
  - Brooke, Albert E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1916-1920; 000148
  - Brooks, G. Shirley. Est. number items = 1-10., 1940-1941; 000149
  - Brooks, James C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1964; 000150
  - Brower, Andrew V. Z. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000151
  - Brower, Auburn Edward. Est. number items = 50+., 1934-1982; 000152
  - Brower, John H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1974; 000153
  - Brower, Lincoln P. Est. number items = 50+., 1951-1993; 000154
  - Brown, A. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925-1926; 000155
  - Brown, Edward C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000156
  - Brown, F. Martin. Est. number items = 50+., 1937-1986; 000157
  - Brown, Keith S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965-1994; 000158
  - Brown, Kirby W. Est. number items = 21-50., 1969-1983; 000159
  - Brown, Lauren. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 000160
  - Brown, Paul. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972-1973; 000161
  - Brown, R. GB. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000162
  - Brown, Vinson. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000163
  - Brown, W. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945-1961; 000164
  - Brown, William L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1951; 000165
  - Brown, William. Est. number items = 1-10., 1977; 000166
  - Browne, Carey. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000167
  - Browne, L. Barton. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000168
  - Bruce, Victor. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000169
  - Brues, C. T. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1953; 000170
  - Bryk, Felix. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1952; 000171
  - Brylski, P. V. Est. number items = 1-10., 000172
  - Bucholz, Otto. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1957; 000173
  - Buck, Paul H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 000174
  - Buettner-Janusch, John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000175
  - Bulgren, Dale A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1938; 000176
  - Bull, Alice Lou. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000177
  - Bullini, Luciano. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1987; 000178
  - Burden, G. S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963; 000180
  - Burdick, William N. Est. number items = 21-50., 1952-1957; 000181
  - Burgess, J. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976; 000182
  - Burkhardt, Dietrich. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984-1986; 000183
  - Burks, Barnard D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1946-1947; 000184
  - Burlin, Jack. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000185
  - Burns, John M. Est. number items = 11-20., 1957-1966; 000186
  - Burrows, Frances. Est. number items = 1-10., 1917; 000187
  - Bush, Guy L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1968; 000188
  - Butler, Robert. Est. number items = 11-20., 1957-1964; 000189
  - Bye, Robert Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1991; 000190
  - Byers, George W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1959-1978; 000191
  - Caccone, Adalgisa. Est. number items = 1-10., 000192
  - Cadbury, John W. 3rd. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1951; 000193
  - Cadiou, John M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000194
  - Cady, Michael E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000195
  - Cain, Arthur J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000196
  - Calkins, Virgil F. Est. number items = 11-20., 1935-1936; 000197
  - Callaghan, Curtis J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962-1970; 000198
  - Callaghan, G. F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000199
  - Callaghan, Philip. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1965; 000200
  - Calvert, Philip P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948; 000201
  - Calvo, Javier Gonzalo Perez. Est. number items = 1-10., 1986-1987; 000202
  - Canete, Anatolia. Est. number items = 1-10., 1945; 000226
  - Cantor, Susan. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000203
  - Carcasson, R. H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960; 000204
  - Carde, Ring. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957-1960; 000205
  - Carey, David B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1989; 000206
  - Carpenter, Albert J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1955; 000207
  - Carpenter, Frank M. Est. number items = 50+., 1943-1986; 000208
  - Carpenter, G. D. Hale. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1953; 000209
  - Carpenter, S. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 000210
  - Carpentier, Fritz. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000211
  - Carr, Elaine. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964-1967; 000212
  - Carr, F. M. B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000213
  - Carr, Linda. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961-1962; 000214
  - Carson, Hampton L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1977; 000215
  - Caruthers, Morris E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 000216
  - Cary, Margaret M. Est. number items = 50+., 1948-1964; 000217
  - Cary-Curtis, John &. Barbara. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1969; 000218
  - Casher, Leslie E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000219
  - Cass, Charles L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1915-1918; 000220
  - Casselberry, R. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1947; 000221
  - Cassidy, George L. Est. number items = 1-10., 000222
  - Cassino, Samuel E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1934; 000223
  - Cavanaugh, Robert W. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963; 000224
  - Cazier, Mont A. Est. number items = 11-20., 1948-1957; 000225
  - Chadwick, Leigh E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1953-1957; 000227
  - Chambers, Donald S. Est. number items = 10., 1961-1965; 002790
  - Chandler, George. Est. number items = 1-10., 1934; 000228
  - Chandless, Richard C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1954; 000229
  - Chapin, Edward A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1953; 000230
  - Charlton, A. C. R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000231
  - Chase, E. P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1915-1922; 000232
  - Chase, Hazel. Est. number items = 1-10., 000233
  - Cheng, Fung Y. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000234
  - Chermock, Frank. Est. number items = 11-20., 1942-1953; 000235
  - Chermock, Ralph L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950-1963; 000236
  - Chester, Terry L. Est. number items = 11-20., 1975-1990; 000237
  - Chew, Frances. Est. number items = 21-50., 1971-1983; 000238
  - China, W. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000239
  - Chitty, F. John. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1955; 000240
  - Chojnacki, Stanislaw. Est. number items = 21-50., 1957-1967; 000241
  - Christiansen, Kenneth. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1953; 000242
  - Christie, L. Est. number items = 21-50., 1959-1966; 000243
  - Chua, C. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967; 000244
  - Claridge, Michael F. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1986; 000245
  - Clark, Austin H. Est. number items = 21-50., 1933-1952; 000246
  - Clark, Cyril A. Est. number items = 50+., 1952-1988; 000247
  - Clarke, Bryan C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1967; 000248
  - Clarke, Gowan C. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1962; 000249
  - Clarke, J. F. Gates. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1969; 000250
  - Clarke, Louis C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000251
  - Classey, E. W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1953-1959; 000252
  - Cleland, Ralph E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966; 000253
  - Clement, Ian D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000254
  - Clement, Ronald C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1994-1997; 000255
  - Clench, Carleton W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000256
  - Clench, Harry K. Est. number items = 50+., 1942-1975; 000257
  - Clifford, Carleton M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000258
  - Cockerell, T. D. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941-1948; 000259
  - Coddington, Jonathan A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1976-1986; 000260
  - Coe, Charles H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971; 000261
  - Coe, Sophie Dobzhansky. Est. number items = 1-10., 1982; 000262
  - Cohen, Sarah. Est. number items = 1-10., 1995; 000263
  - Coher, Edward I. Est. number items = 21-50., 1943-1965; 000264
  - Coleman, Babette B. &. John R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1962; 000265
  - Coleman, Lionel R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1960-1964; 000266
  - Collins, Donald L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1964; 000267
  - Commerford, L. E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951; 000268
  - Common, Ian F. B. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1976; 000269
  - Comstock, John A. Est. number items = 21-50., 1932-1967; 000270
  - Comstock, William P. Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1953; 000271
  - Concello, Joseph A. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1966-1968; 000272
  - Conde, Bruno. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1956; 000273
  - Conger, Alan D. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000274
  - Conroy, Brian A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1969; 000275
  - Consiglio, Carlo. Est. number items = 1-10., 1973; 000276
  - Cook, Carl. Est. number items = 1-10., 1950; 000277
  - Cook, Edwin F. Est. number items = 11-20., 1949-1963; 000278
  - Cook, Laurence M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959-1988; 000279
  - Cook, Rebecca J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1971-1973; 000280
  - Coolidge, Harold J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1950; 000281
  - Cooper, Kenneth W. Est. number items = 11-20., 1954-1973; 000282
  - Corkwell, Theodore S. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943; 000283
  - Corliss, John O. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1956; 000284
  - Correia Ralha, Alberto Jose. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954; 000285
  - Cottam, Walter P. Est. number items = 1-10., 1941-1967; 000286
  - Cotter, William B. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1964; 000287
  - Cottrell, Annette B. (G. W. ). Est. number items = 11-20., 1950-1978; 000288
  - Cottrell, C. B. "Kit". Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-1984; 000289
  - Coutsis, John G. Est. number items = 21-50., 1954-1987; 000290
  - Covell, Charles V. Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1963-1979; 000291
  - Cowan, I. McT. Est. number items = 1-10., 1957; 000292
  - Crabhill, Ralph E. Jr. Est. number items = 11-20., 1952-1964; 000293
  - Craig, Catherine L. Est. number items = 1-10., 000294
  - Crane, L. Burton Jr. Est. number items = 1-10., 1916; 000295
  - Crane, Will E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1925; 000296
  - Creed, E. Robert. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000297
  - Creelman, James L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1937; 000298
  - Creighton, William S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1958; 000299
  - Crow, Peter N. Est. number items = 1-10., 1959; 000300
  - Crozet, Celestin. Est. number items = 1-10., 000301
  - Cunningham, Richard A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988-1989; 000302
  - Curtis, Christopher C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1965; 000303
  - Cutler, Bruce. Est. number items = 1-10., 1983; 000304
  - D'Antonio, William V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1972; 000305
  - Dahlsten, Donald W. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981-2004; 000307
  - Dahms, E. C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1979; 000308
  - Daly, Howell V. Est. number items = 1-10., 1970; 000309
  - Daniels, Jaret C. Est. number items = 1-10., 1988; 000310
  - Danilevsky, Alexander S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000311
  - Dannreuther, T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1949-1954; 000312
  - Darlington, Herbert S. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955; 000313
  - Darlington, Philip J. Est. number items = 50+., 1948-1968; 000314
  - Dasch, Clement E. Est. number items = 1-10., 1981; 000315
  - David, James H. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000316
  - David, W. A. Est. number items = 1-10., 1961; 000317
  - Davidson, Eugene. Est. number items = 1-10., 1958; 000318
  - Davies, Douglas M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000319
  - Davies, Thomas W. Est. number items = 50+., 1945-1986; 000320
  - Davis, Don R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1973; 000321
  - Davis, Noel. Est. number items = 1-10., 1987; 000322
  - Davis, Norman T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1956; 000323
  - Davis, Robert S. L. Est. number items = 1-10., 1967-1968; 000324
  - Davis, William T. Est. number items = 1-10., 1943; 000325
  - DeCoursey, R. M. Est. number items = 1-10., 1951-1956; 000335
  - DeFoliart, Gene R. Est. number items = 1-10., 1955-1956; 000336
  - DeMasi, Victor. Est. number items = 1-10., 1991; 000338
  - DeVries, Philip J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1984; 000344
  - DeWind, Joan. Est. number items = 1-10., 1980; 000345
  - Dean, Mary Baptista. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1957; 000333
  - Deboutteville, C. Delmare. Est. number items = 1-10., 1948-1950; 000334
  - Delany, M. J. Est. number items = 1-10., 1954-1956; 000337